Ismay, Lou; Papers ua902.064
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Student Writings, 1969-1977; Undated; 4; 11.75 cubic ft.
  - Engler, Virginia, Public Interest Research Groups and their Impaction Environmental Decisions and Litigation, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Ettlinger, Barbara, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Ezak, Christina; Wienstein, Paul; Researching Wild Turkeys in NY State, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Faber, Gerald, Governmental Reform in Long Beach, 1972 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Fagen, Michael, What Happens to Seniors? Random Survey, 1977 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Faring, John, untitled, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Farrell, Marilyn; Maher, Kathleen; Mullin, Thomas; Vonstein, Gary; Grabon vs. NY State Water Resources Commission, 1972 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Farina, John, Aquatic Environment and the Urbin Complex, 1977 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)
  - Feigenbaum, Steven Sketches of Lectures, 1970 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 14)
  - Fein, Mindy, The SST Concorde, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Feinberg, Ellen, Surface Mining in the U.S., 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Feinberg, Peter, Adaptations for Flight in Birds, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Feingersh, Rose, A Children's Story, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Feinstein, Ronald, Air pollution, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Feldman, Gloria, The Animal World of the American Indians, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Feldman, Stuart Paul, NYS Workmen's Compensation Law, 1972 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21)
  - Fenimore, Teresa, Conservation of Energy Insulation, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 22)
  - Fenimore, Teresa, The Energy Crisis, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 23)
  - Fink, David, Independent Study, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 24)
  - Fink, Dave, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 25)
  - Fitzgerald, Kevin, Smallness, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 26)
  - Fitzsimmons, Mary Ellen, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 27)
  - Fonda, Jeffrey, The Diesel; Tomorrow, Power Source of the Future, 1972 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 28)
  - Fondario, Debra, Land Use and Surface Strip Mining, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 29)
  - Formanek, Dave; Garfinkel, Mark, Dome Report #1, 1971 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30)
  - Forrester, Bo,b Journal, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 31)
  - Forrester, Robert, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - Fortran, Roderick, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33)
  - Foster Karen; Murphy, Sharon; Steiner, Christine; An investigation of Urban Renewal In Downtown Albany, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 34)
  - Frandina, Dara, Wildlife Conservation, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 35)
  - Freed, David, Recycle your Recyclables, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36)
  - Fromer, Leonard, Environmental Forum Project, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 37)
  - Frumkin, Yvette, Mouse Project, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - Fry, Jeffrey, Common Technological Methods in Solar Heating, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - Gabitz, Leslie, Final, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40)
  - Galbreth, Elizabeth, Sovereign Immunity: A Case in Point, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 41)
  - Galbreth, Elizabeth, untitled, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - Galietta, Gabe, The Rights of Prisoners, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 43)
  - Gamelsky, Lee, recycling Incentives and Disincentives, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 44)
  - Gardner, Ronald, Draft Violators are Justified in not Participating in the Vietnam War, 1972 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 45)
  - Garett, Glenn, Fault or No -- Fault Insurance?, 1972 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 46)
  - Gasser, George, The Allocation of Justice in the Local Legal System, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 47)
  - Gavagan, James, The NY State Conservationist, 1970 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 48)
  - Gefers, Frederick, Final, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 49)
  - Gelb, Eric, Branzburg v. Hayes: Constitutional Rights of Newsmen, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 50)
  - Geraei, Mary, Abortion, 1972 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 51)
  - Gerbitz, Gail, Beauty and Health: Natural Cosmetics, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 52)
  - Gibb, John, Journal, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 53)
  - Gilday, Nancy, Independent Study, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 54)
  - Giordana, Thomas; Sylvester, Michael; Wachs, Stuart, Organic and Inorganic Nutrient Wastes, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 55)
  - Gleicher, Andrea, untitled, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 56)
  - Glickenhaus, Michael; Frishberg, Judy Investigation of Area Campgrounds, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 57)
  - Goldfarb, Jeffrey, Pure Waters Movement, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 58)
  - Goldmacher, Beth, We've Been Warned, 1971 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 59)
  - Goldman, Karen, Airport Noise Pollution, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 60)
  - Goldofsky, Sheldon, The Coliform Test As an Indication of Water Pollution, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 61)
  - Goldstein, Arthur, untitled, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 62)
  - Goldstein, Jonathon, The Reverands Daniel and Philip Berrigan vs. the US, 1972 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 63)
  - Grabon, John; McCarg, Clifford; White, Joseph; The Importance of the Environmental Quality Bond Act of 1972 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 64)
  - Grady, Patricia, Log, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 65)
  - Grady, Patricia, Wetlands Survey, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 66)
  - Graham, Bonni,e untitled, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 67)
  - Grant, Michelle, The Effects of Granola, Wonder Bread and Mouse Chow on Laboratory Mice, 1977 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 68)
  - Green, Brian, The Rivers and Harbors Act of 1899 as Environmental Law, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 69)
  - Green, Brian; Di caprio, Joseph; Campout in the Adirondacks, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 70)
  - Green, Robert, Dialogue, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 71)
  - Greenbaum, Amy, Guide to the Hearing Process, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 72)
  - Greenberg, Ellen, untitled, 1970 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 73)
  - Greenberg, Keith, Slides, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 74)
  - Greenberg, Keith; Pinchuk, Neil; A Study of Nassau County, NY Drinking and Recreational Waters, 1977 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 75)
  - Greenberg, Shari, Food and Drug Laws; Protection or Deception?, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 76)
  - Greenberg, Shari, Plants and Colored Lights, 1974 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 77)
  - Greenberg, Shari, untitled, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 78)
  - Greenwald, Gary, Environment and the Library, 1976 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 79)
  - Griffin, Maldonia, Attica Prisoners Rights, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 80)
  - Grinager, Nicoline, Natural Foods Project, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 81)
  - Grinager, Nicoline, Wild Foods, 1971 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 82)
  - Gross, Todd; Metz, Jeremy; Experiments and Considerations of the Acid Rain Problem in the Capital District, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 83)
  - Grzybowski, Gary, No Fault Insurance, 1972 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 84)
  - Gumbs, Carmen, Divorce and the Law in NY State, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 85)
  - Gundersen, Edna, Environment has two sides that are one, 1970 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 86)
  - Guran, Elizabeth, Plant Care, 1973 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 87)
  - Gutman, Paul; Segerstrom, Richard, The Abortion Issue, Undated (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 88)
  - Gutowski, James, The Case Against Anti-Automobile Legislation, 1970 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 89)
  - Guzik, Howard, An Analysis of Cerebral Spinal Defects in New York State, 1975 (Box 4 (4-Student Writings), Folder 90)
  - Haas, Jack; Leyonmark, Gail; Messing, Ira; Toppel, Mitchell; Changing a Chemically Treated Garden into a Organic Garden, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Hall, Mike, Hiking Trails, 1975 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Halloran, Joh,n Historical background and Architectural Survey of Cohoes, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Hamburg, Michelle, Environmental Law, 1976 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Hamdan, Maha, The Aswan Dam: Pros & Cons, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Hanasik, Betty; Eden, Edward; The Effect of Germicides on the Biodegradability of Soaps, 1974 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Harps, Terrance, The Black Panther Party, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Harrington, Joann; Schustek, Samuel; Cohen, Victor; A dining Guide to the Albany Area, 1974 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Hass, Michael; Coven, Richard; A Commuter Analysis of the Mass Transportation Systems of New York City and Montreal, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Hawkins, Brenn An Investigative Analysis v. The Urban Environment, 1977 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Hawrys, Linda, What's in our Waterways?, 1976 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Heckman, J. Paul, The Blue Laws: A review, 1973 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Heller, Minette, The Inequities of Custody, 1972 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)
  - Herbert, Stephen; Menendez, Dennis; Cohoes Water Falls Area, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 14)
  - Herkowits, Gail, untitled, 1975 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Herskowitz, Susan, The Validity of Environmental Legislation: Parellel Developments in Land-use Rights, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Herskowitz, Susan, untitled, 1977 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Hessenthaler, Debra; Kirilean Photography of Plant Leaves, 1974 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Environmental Legislation Study Group, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Hirsch, Felice Nancy, Returnable Bottle Legislation, 1976 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Hirsh, Robert, Noise Ordinances, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21)
  - Hochberg, Andy, Photos, 1970 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 22)
  - Hogan, Elizabeth, Forest Policy, Law, and Administration and Overview, 1975 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 23)
  - Holland, Mark, Mercury Contamination of the Aquatic Environment, 1975 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 24)
  - Hollander, Penni, Plant and Animal Life Diary, 1973 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 25)
  - Hollander, Penni; Greenblatt, Paul; Hong, Glenn; The Analysis of Phenal Concentrations in the Hudson River, 1972 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 26)
  - Hood, Charles, untitled, 1973 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 27)
  - Hopkins, Mary Louise, A Personal Learning Experience through the Natural Environment, 1970 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 28)
  - Horne, Dian,e Discrimination, 1972 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 29)
  - Hornick, Amy, Log G.E. Plant Project, 1974 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30)
  - Horowitz, Joyce, The Moral Question of Zero Population Growth and Birth Control, 1975 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 31)
  - Howard, Ernestine, Approach to the Gang Problem through Community Organization and Youth Services Administration, 1975 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - Howard, Ernestine, Tina Dedication, 1977 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33)
  - Hower, Richard, Energy: An Introduction, 1971 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 34)
  - Hughley, Frank, Why We Should preserve Our Natural Resources, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 35)
  - Hyman, Diana, Environmental Health in African Regions, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36)
  - Iervolino, Susan, Project NYPIRG, 1976 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 37)
  - Iervolino, Susan, Study of the Helderberg Escarpment, 1976 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - Incomplete Papers 1975, 1976; Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - Isaacs, Marc, The Chicago Eight Conspiracy Trial, 1972 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40)
  - Ishkanian, Mark, NYEN Articles, 1974 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 41)
  - Ives, Valerie, untitled, 1972 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - Izzo, Charles, Juvenile Court, 1972 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 43)
  - Jackson, Janice, Abortions, 1972 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 44)
  - Jackson, Lynne, Recycling, 1973 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 45)
  - Jackson, Lynne, Waterways, 1974-1976 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 46)
  - Jacobs, Nancy, A Report on Noise, 1976 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 47)
  - Jahn, Cynthia, Citizens Standing to Sue in Environmental Litigation, 1973 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 48)
  - James, Eldon, Crisis in Solid Waste Disposal, 1972 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 49)
  - Johnson, Clarence, The Law and the Senior Citizens, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 50)
  - Johnson, Susan, How Friendly is the Atom, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 51)
  - Jones, Mary C., The Affect of Algae on Water Supplies, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 52)
  - Juntunsen, Linda, untitled, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 53)
  - Kaigler, Minnie, The Black Women's Role in the Struggle for Women's Rights, 1973 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 54)
  - Kalogerakos, Harry, Land use Planning Act of 1974, 1975 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 55)
  - Kaloun, James, untitled, 1977 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 56)
  - Kamin, Edward, Overcrowding as it Affects Social Behavior, 1969 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 57)
  - Kaplan, David, Tanzman, Esther, Photo-essay, 1973 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 58)
  - Kaplan, Ellen; Katz, Bill; Salon, Rebecca; Scrapbook, 1972 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 59)
  - Kaplan, Gary, Radioactive Wastes from Nuclear Energy, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 60)
  - Kaplan, Marilyn, Hydropathy or Let Water Cure You!, 1972 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 61)
  - Kaplan, Robin, Noise: An In-Depth Study, 1976 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 62)
  - Kaplowitz, Harvey, A Technical Environmental and Legal Study of Noise Pollution and Airports, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 63)
  - Karl, Roz; Murphy, Pat; Nolte, Jean; A Guide for the Upper-Level High School Course, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 64)
  - Kasoff, Barry, Air Pollution and the American Social System, 1977 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 65)
  - Kasoff, Barry, What Society is Missing by being Totally Dependent Upon Science and Technology, 1977 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 66)
  - Katatsky, Eileen, Ecology House, 1973 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 67)
  - Katz, Jeff, Where Do the Children Play, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 68)
  - Katz, Walt, No -- Fault Auto Insurance, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 69)
  - Kearns, John, City of Amsterdam Recreation Survey, 1977 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 70)
  - Kearns, John, on the Value of Subtraction, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 71)
  - Keller, Barbara, Environmental Guide to SUNY Albany, 1977 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 72)
  - Kellogg, Richard, Visual Blight and its Control in Poestenkill, NY, 1970 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 73)
  - Kelly, Robert, David v. Goliath or Kelly v. Sears, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 74)
  - Kennedy, Jean, untitled, 1975 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 75)
  - Kennedy, Jean; Moran, Peg; Matise, Michelle, Food Store Survey, 1974 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 76)
  - Kernan, Mathew, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 77)
  - Kerwin, Karen, Independent Study, 1976 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 78)
  - Kesselman, Paul, Is it Noise?, Undated (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 79)
  - Klein, David, Final, 1976 (Box 5 (4-Student Writings), Folder 80)
  - Klein, Linda, Suggestions, Criticisms, and Reactions to Recommended Ideas for the Indian Quad Food Service, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Klein, Michael, The Dowsing Phenomenon, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Knapp, Gerald, The Environmental Effect of Forest Fire, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Knapp, Jerry, The Grassy Point Marsh: How Valuable is it?, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Koch, Alan, Journal -- Waterways, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Koehler, Bart, Scum Along the Mohawks Cayadutta, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Koenig, Renate, Final, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Koeppel, Peter; Seiberg, Craig Analysis of Air Pollution in the Albany Area, 1975 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Kohlohaff, Kenneth, untitled, 1972 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Komarin, Gary, The Layman's Guide to Environmental Thinking, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)
  - Korngold, Michael, Term Report, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 11)
  - Koss, Ronald, Are There Places for Us?, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 12)
  - Kowalchyk, John, Independent Study, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 13)
  - Kowalchyk, John, Journal, 1977 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 14)
  - Kowalski, Victoria, Organizations Concerned with Issues Related to Over Population, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 15)
  - Kramer, Barbara, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 16)
  - Kranick, Diane, The Schenectady Stockade, 1975 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 17)
  - Kreuter, William, Independent Study, 1977 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 18)
  - Kreuter, William,project on Land Use Planning in the Town of Guilderland NY, 1977 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 19)
  - Kreuter, William, 1975 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 20)
  - Kropf, Barbara, Open Space Preservation and Regulation, 1975 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 21)
  - Kroplick, Lois; Rafal, Keith; Frequency of Palmar Creases Among a random Sample of 200 Students: Our Experiences at Willowbrook and CDPC, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 22)
  - Kruszewski, Mark Bogs: A Survey and Study, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 23)
  - Kruszewski, Mark Black Pond: Analysis of a Dune top Depression, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 24)
  - Kruzan, Kathryn, Being Concerned with Ways of Introducing for Discussion and Action some problems of survival, 1970 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 25)
  - Kupersmith, Leonard Alaska: A Developing Crisis, 1975 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 26)
  - Kurtz, Ken, University Lake, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 27)
  - Lafferty, James; Alper, Carol; Cleaning the Lake Area, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 28)
  - Lagna, Lorraine, Journal, 1970 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 29)
  - Lagna, Lorraine, A Study of Beach Plant Life in Relation to its Environment, 1971 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 30)
  - Laster, Rosie, Environmental Systems Analysis: A Personal Definition, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 31)
  - Lazzara, Allen; Laravie, Joe; Salerni, Eugene; Adirondack State Park Land Plan, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 32)
  - Leder, Robert, American Indian Dwellings, 1974 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 33)
  - Leder, Robert, Lamb's Quarters, 1977 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 34)
  - Lessu, William, 1977 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 35)
  - Letter to Alumni, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 36)
  - Levenson, Jonathon, The People vs. The Machine, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 37)
  - Levenson, Jonathon, Presidential Politics at SUNYA, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 38)
  - Levey, Barbara, Noise Pollution, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 39)
  - Levin, Brian, The Effects of Phosphates on Algae, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 40)
  - Levine Mark, Truck Noise, 1974 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 41)
  - Levine Mark, Truck Noise 2, 1974 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 42)
  - Levine, Richard, Final, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 43)
  - Levitan, Daniel, Correctional Legislation in the New York State Legislature, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 44)
  - Lewis, Aaron, Conclusions on Systems Dynamics, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 45)
  - Lichtman, Kenneth, A Survey of the New York Times Editorial Policy on Environmental Issues, 1968-1975 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 46)
  - Lichtman, Kenneth, Land use Legislation, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 47)
  - Lichtman, Kenneth, Should the Federal Government Finance the Development of New Towns?, 1977 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 48)
  - Lieb, Mindy, The Delmar Wildlife Research Laboratory, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 49)
  - Linden, Neil, The Time To Hear, 1970 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 50)
  - Lindh, Joel; Colangelo, Regina; General Electric Project, 1972 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 51)
  - Lipnack, Richard; Rabin, Keith; The Politics of Ecology, 1974 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 52)
  - Lippacher, Alice, The West Canada Creek, 1973 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 53)
  - Litwak, Steve, Perspective Contributions: An Essay on Environmental Hope, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 54)
  - Lopez, Henry, Organic Farming, 1975 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 55)
  - Loris, Paulette, The Equal Rights Amendment, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 56)
  - Lorring, Dedra, -- Anne Environmental Impact, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 57)
  - Lorring, Debbie, Journal -- Solar Energy Project, 1977 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 58)
  - Lorring, Debra, -- Anne untitled, 1976 (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 59)
  - Lubert, Stuart, Systems Analysis; History of Science, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 60)
  - Lyon's Michael, Plankton Competition Along Six Mile Reservoir, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 61)
  - Lyons, Ralph, A Mini Course Prepared for Environmental Forum, Undated (Box 6 (4-Student Writings), Folder 62)
  - Madhavan, V., To Control Pollution, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 1)
  - Magnien, Robert, Acid Precipitation; Causes, Effects, and Controls, 1976 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 2)
  - Malgieri, Kurt, Feasibility of Protein from the Cultivation and Harvesting of Algae, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 3)
  - Mallory, Joyce, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 4)
  - Malone, Steve, The American Prison Problem, 1973 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 5)
  - Manning, Kevin, Exam, 1977 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 6)
  - Marchesiello, Joseph South West Africa, 1972 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 7)
  - Marcus, Ira; Plescow, Stephen; Open Space Index: East Greenbush, NY, 1976 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 8)
  - Marcus, Ira, untitled, 1974 (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 9)
  - Marinello, Elaine, Solar Cooker Design and Technology, Undated (Box 7 (4-Student Writings), Folder 10)